fpsb.co.in 2015-12-31

# FPSB India - FPSB India Team

(Version 1.0, effective 01 November 2008)

This privacy policy sets out how Financial Planning Standards Board India (FPSB India) uses and protects information that you give us when you use this website. FPSB India is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information we ask for will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy. FPSB India may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. Make sure that you are familiar with our current privacy policy. If you have questions or concerns, please contact us at:

Financial Planning Standards Board India   
702, 7th Floor, Leela Business Park,  
Andheri-Kurla Road, Andheri (East).  
Mumbai. India - 400 059.  
Tel : +91 22 6171 2424  
Fax : +91 22 6171 2444  
Email : [admin@fpsbindia.org](mailto:admin@fpsb.org)

Your privacy is important to us. To protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about how your information is collected and used. Our privacy policy is accessible from our homepage and at every point where your personal information may be requested.

For users of the public portions of FPSB India’s website, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from you as you visit our website. Our Privacy Policy applies to information collected or submitted by you in certain other sections of FPSB India’s website. We only collect information from you that are relevant to our needs.

The type of personal information that FPSB may collect includes:

First Name  
Last Name  
Organization Name  
Contact Address  
Phone  
E-mail address  
Credit Card No. etc. 

FPSB India does not share, sell, distribute or transfer your personal information to outside parties unless we have your permission to do so or are required by law. We gather personal information from you to populate our contact management system so that we can better track our one-time or ongoing dealings with you. We use return email addresses to answer emails we receive and to confirm that the personal information we have collected from you is accurate, complete and current. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties, including FPSB India’s Certificants or Students unless FPSB India needs one or more of its Certificants or Students to assist in responding to your request. We never use or share personal information you provide to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described in this section without your consent.

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To protect against loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, FPSB India has put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our website contains links to other websites that may be of interest to you. When using these links to exit our site, recognize that FPSB India does not have any control over these other websites. FPSB India is not responsible for the protection and privacy of any personal information you provide when visiting these sites, which are not governed by FPSB India’s privacy policy. You should familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of these other sites prior to providing personal information.

FPSB India’s Students and Certificants can access personal information online using FPSB India’s Online Certification Management System (OCMS). Members can correct factual errors in personal information by sending us a request that shows error. To protect the privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to the Online Certification Management system (OCMS) or making corrections. The users of other services e.g. Financial Planning Journal Subscribers can have their information corrected by sending a request to [journal@fpsbindia.org](mailto:journal@fpsbindia.org) or [info@fpsbindia.org](mailto:info@fpsbindia.org) or [admin@fpsbindia.org](mailto:admin@fpsbindia.org).

Due to the burden that would be placed on FPSB India by allowing casual contacts access to correct, amend or delete personal information provided to FPSB India during one-time website inquiries, FPSB India does not provide these individuals with access to information stored by FPSB India. If you are not comfortable with this policy, you should not use our website.

If you have questions or concerns about our privacy policy, or if you would like to complain to FPSB India, please write to us at [admin@fpsbindia.org](mailto:admin@fpsbindia.org)
